Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Group 3, Series II: Manuscripts
  - Smart Loving, Intelligence is the Ultimate Aphrodisiac manuscript - Leary, Timothy pt. 1, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Smart Loving, Intelligence is the Ultimate Aphrodisiac manuscript - Leary, Timothy pt. 2, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Coming of Age in the Age of AIDS - David Leavitt, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Skin Bled - Peter Lewis pt. 1, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Skin Bled - Peter Lewis pt. 2, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jack Smith - An Introduction - Leffingwell, Edward, July 23, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The Son of a Murderer - Limonov, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Oriental Girls Desire Romance - Liu, Catherine ch. 1-4, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Oriental Girls Desire Romance - Liu, Catherine ch. 5-9, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Oriental Girls Desire Romance - Liu, Catherine ch. 10-12, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - High Risk Submission - Poem: Liu, Tomothy, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - The Story of my Father - Lopate, Phillip, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Linmark, Zamora R. - Leche, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sensory for Nine - Zamora, Linmark, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - The Subject Steve - Sam Lipsyte pt. 1, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The Subject Steve - Sam Lipsyte pt. 2, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - High Risk Submission - Poems: Maresca, John, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Berlin, Bromley - Bertie Marshall, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Memories - Manrique, Jamie, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Outline of My Lover - Douglas Martin, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Dr. Haggard's Disease - McGrath, Patrick pt. 1, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Dr. Haggard's Disease - McGrath, Patrick pt. 2, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Haggard's Disease - McGrath, Patrick pt. 3, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - McKinney, Casey - excerpts from untitled novel and Dennis Cooper cover letter, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - I Really Want to See You - Meer, Ameena, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 1, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 2, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 3, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 1, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 2, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 3, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 1, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 2, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mud That Walks - Stewart Meyer pt. 3, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Paul - Correspondence and excerpts from manuscripts, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Looking for a New Last Name - Mitchell, Larry, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - House Music - Bob Morris, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Untitled - Bob Morris, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Real - Bob Morris and Hilton Als, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Playdate - Bob Morris and Karen Balliet, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Poetry and Prose by Bob Mould, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Shopping Cart Soldiers - Mulligan, John pt. 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Shopping Cart Soldiers - Mulligan, John pt. 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Shopping Cart Soldiers - Mulligan, John pt. 3, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Don't Try This at Home - Navarro, Dave and Strauss, Neil, June, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - High Risk Submission - Poems: Newnington, Nina Crow, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Ugly Beauty - Glenn O'Brien, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cursed from Birth pt 1. - David Ohle, August 21, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Cursed from Birth pt 2. - David Ohle, August 21, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cursed from Birth pt 3. - David Ohle, August 21, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Cursed from Birth pt 4. - David Ohle, August 21, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Cursed from Birth - David Ohle, September 17, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Exemplary Life of the Slave and the Master - draft w - Otero, Manuel Ramos, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - To Abea and Back Again - Partido, Suzette, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Cattle Call - Chuck Palahniuk, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Utopia Limited pt. 1 - Tony Peake, August, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Utopia Limited pt. 2 - Tony Peake, August, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Utopia Limited pt. 3 - Tony Peake, August, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - The Playful World - Pesce, Mark pt. 1, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Playful World - Pesce, Mark pt. 2, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Playful World - Pesce, Mark pt. 3, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cocksucker Blues - Homes, A.M. and Throwing Shade - Pinckney, Daryl, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - How Dare You Even Think These Things - Preston, John, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Submissions for Portable Lower East Side, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Coming to the North - Porter, Veneita (3rd Draft), undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Novale project Proposal - Proctor, Minna, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pullinger, Kate - submissions for High Risk, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Jack Smith Photographer - Rinder, Lawrence, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Beckett manuscript - Rosset, Barney, May, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Armed Response - Rower, Ann, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Real Life Entertaining - Rubell, Jennifer, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - High Risk Submission: Poems - Saint, Assoto, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Are You Ready to Rock? - Sapphire, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Emailed manuscript (title unknown) - Savage, Jon, May, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Schambelan, Elizabeth - Manuscripts: Elsa Schiaparelli's Visions of the Modern Age; Star '84; Superstar Tips, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Deception - Sellers, Terence, August, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Is There Life After Sadomasochism? - Sellers, Terence, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript (Mistress Manslaughter) - Sellers, Terence, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - To Achieve Death - Sellers, Terence, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - The Story of # 9 - Simon, Lizzie, June 8, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Trance: Part II - Sorrentino, Christopher, December, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Odessey and Oracle: The Musical - Strauss, Neil, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - High Risk Submission: Mary, Mary - Sweeney, Emma, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Chain - Ronald Tavel, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Tavel, Ron - Untitled Writings, July 25, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - High Risk Submission: Poems - Tayson, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - High Risk Submission: Poems - Tierney, Karl, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Home Sick (excerpt) Lynne Tillman, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - 9 Cigarettes - David Trinidad, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Anne Sexton - David Trinidad (annotated), undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Bewitched - Trinidad, David, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - My Lover - Trinidad, David, undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - High Risk Submission: David Trinidad - A Photograph; Eighteen to Twenty-One, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Deathcats - Valenzuela, Luisa, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - La Travesia - Valenzuela, Luisa pt. 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - La Travesia - Valenzuela, Luisa pt. 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Voice Literary Supplement Anthology of Writing (proposal), 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Critique of Pure Hipness - Waters, Lindsay, September 25, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Weissman, Benjamin - Submissions for High Risk 2, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - High Risk - David Wojnarowicz submission from Being Queer in America, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - The Cockettes - Worman, Martin, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The Cockettes - Worman, Martin, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Niagara - Woronov, Mary, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Mini Tremble Fits - Wray, Tara, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Lights on Broadway - Wynne, John, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Victory Garden - Wynne, John, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - I, A Loner or Who's a Dyke - Yablonsky, Linda, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Oh Dear; Don't Feel Sorry for Me; She Goes Shopping - Linda Yablonsky, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lethality - Young, Elizabeth and The Deconstruction of the World, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Etiquette templates - author unknown, April 30, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - I am the Fly - author unknown, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Thongs - author unknown, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Those Were Your Words Not Mine - unknown author, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Manuscripts - author and title unknown, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript - author and title unknown, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Group 3, Series III: Affiliations
  - Academy of American Poets Luncheon, November 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1987, May 18 1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - American Playwrights Dinner, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Center, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - CLMP Binder, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - CLMP, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - CLMP, October 10, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - CLMP, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - CLMP, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Creative Capital funded projects folder, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Donations, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - National Poetry Month Material - Academy of American Poets, April 2002 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - New School MFA, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - New School University MFA Creative Writing meeting minutes and writing samples, April 2002 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - New School, April 26, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - New School Creative Writing Program, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - New York Writers Conference, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - PEN American Center - correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - PEN AIDS Benefit, November 1990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - PEN American Center - newsletter, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - PEN American Center, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - PEN American Center, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - PEN Agenda and Minutes, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - PEN Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - The PEN American Center Newsletter 94, July 1997 - August 97 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - PEN Literary Awards packet, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - PEN American Center, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - PEN American Center, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - PEN meeting agenda, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - PEN American Center, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - PEN American Center, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - PEN American Center, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - PEN American Center meeting re. A Wind Done Gone, June 2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - PEN American Center, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - PEN Literary Gala, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - PEN Literary Gala pamphlet and contact info, April 2002 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - SOHO House membership, June 2004 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - WNBA (Women's National Book Association), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Group 3, Series IV: Business/Administration Files
  - Subseries A: General Business/Administration Files
    - Acker, Katy - interview (with Lotringer, Sylvere), undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Kathy Acker, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Kathy Acker, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Kathy Acker, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Kathy Acker - photos and dream drawings, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Address List, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Materials, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Advertising, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Agreements/Contracts, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Agreement - Serpent's Tail, New Left, RE/SEARCH, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Awards: Rolling Stone, Lambda, National M.S. Society, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Book jackets, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - BP Report Vol II No. 17, March 31, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Udo Breger article photos, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Catalog, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - City Lights 40th anniversary, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - City Lights '96 titles, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - City Lights Books, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - City Lights Books new titles, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - City Lights Books new titles, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - City Lights galley mailings, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - City Lights Pocket Poets Anthology, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - City Lights Publications, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Coach House Press, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Coach House publication announcements, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Contracts, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Contract - Twin Cities Public Television, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Cover proof - The Oblivion Seekers, undated (1975) (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Damon and Naomi picture, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Datebook and address book, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Date book, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Donadio and Olsen, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - e-Journal and book tour info for Nearly Roadkill - Sullivan, Caitlin and Bornstein, Kate, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - The Evergreen Review Reader and The Olympia Reader, undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Photos - Bart Everly, undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Book Profiles (Exact Change), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Exact Change PR, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Exact Change PR, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Exact Change - sales kit, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Exact Change Yearbook no. 1 - publicity, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Exact Change Yearbook no. 1 - reviews, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Exact Change Yearbook no. 1, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Expenses - James Grauerholz, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Fales contract, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Fales donation note, undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Galley mailing, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Galley mailings, undated (1995) (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Galley mailing, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Galley mailing, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - John Giorno Band, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - John Giorno folder, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - John Giorno folder, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Photos - John Giorno, undated (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Giorno Poetry Systems - Poets and Artists with AIDS Fund grants, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Annita Griner, undated (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Grove Press client list, March 9, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Grove Press Drama News, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Grove Press Expenses, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Grove Press projects, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Grove Press - press releases, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Grove Press - press releases, 1987-1989 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Gutter Press launch, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - High Risk agreement and mission statement, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - High Risk - catalogs, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - High Risk - contracts, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - High Risk drafts - part 1, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - High Risk drafts - part 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - High Risk drafts - part 3, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - High Risk editor statement drafts, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - High Risk - financial statements, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - High Risk mailing list, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - High Risk notes, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - High Risk permissions, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - High Risk proofs, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - High Risk proof (photocopies) part 1, September 25, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - High Risk proof (photocopies) part 2, September 25, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - High Risk proof (photocopies) part 3, September 25, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - High Risk - proposal, intro, notes, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - High Risk photos, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - High Risk readings, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - High Risk submission - Keith Haring Sketches, January, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - High Risk - submissions index and demographics, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - High Risk - table of contents and author bios, June 1990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - High Risk 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - High Risk 2 agreement Letter for Dr. Haggard's Disease, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - High Risk 2 British tax exemption, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - High Risk 2 contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - High Risk 2 contributor notes, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - High Risk 2 cover art, intro, T.o C., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - High Risk 2 mailing lists, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - High Risk 2 mailing lists, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - High Risk 2 permission agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Henry Holt new fiction catalogue, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Hit List..., undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Incommunicado Press - releases/publicity, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Itinerary - Northern Europe, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Keys to the Garden, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - The Kitchen, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - The Kitchen, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Kolovakos Award, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Magic Hour PR, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Memo book - I.S.C. (appointment book), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - 10 year anniversary party packet, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Memos, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Meeting minutes, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Meeting minutes/memos, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Mind Grenades - Plunkett, John and Rossetto, Louis, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - The National Book Awards, November 2001 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 1989 National Book Awards and personal correspondence (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - NEA, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - NEA, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - NEA Grant, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - NEA Grant proposal - correspondence and forms, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - NEA Grants and funding structure, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Notebook, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Notes and Mailing list, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Notes and scraps, August 1997 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - NYS Department of Labor - I.S.C., 1995 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - New York Times - Social Depressives, January 25, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Permission for Discontents, and correction sheets for publishers, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Phone book, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Photos, slides, negatives, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Photos - Christopher Makos, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Photo slides - Stockly, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Press release - Against Empire, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Publishing agreement - Holding Our Own, November 8, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Publishing agreement - You Got to Burn to Shine, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Review copy requests - Degostini, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Rights Guide, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Serpent's Tail financial data, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Shareholders' agreement, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Ira Silverberg client list and Donadio and Olson Inc Book Expo titles, undated, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Ira Silverberg Communications publication forms, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Silverberg resignation letter from Grove Press, January 8, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Stationary, undated (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Steerforth Press - releases/publicity, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Stewart, Tabori and Chang status reports and review copy requests, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Stocks - Rightscenter.com, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Jaqueline Susann proofs, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Fred Tomaselli flyer, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Trademark Handbook, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Valley of the Dolls photo, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Various administrative and personal financial records, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - W and N client list, May 4, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - W and N client list, May 4, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund meeting agenda, October, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Article from Wired magazine, January 1996 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Interview with David Wojnarowicz by Sylvere Lotringer, undated (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Wojnarowicz - Spanish publishing rights, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Wylie, Aitken and Stone client list, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - The Other World - Wynne, John, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Subseries B: Client Projects
    - Client project: Kathy Acker - contracts, royalties: Anglo-Saxon Culture and Shit, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Client project: A Brief Note on Texts Other Than My Own - Acker, Kathy. Contracts for Empire of the Senseless, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Client project: Don Quixote press packet, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker mailing requests, book tour info, correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker galley mailing, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker expenses, itineraries, correspondence, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker publicity packet (photos, reviews), 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Client project: Don Quixote - Kathy Acker financial data and mailing list, 1986-1989 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Client project: Literal Madness - Kathy Acker mailing info and review copy requests, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Client project: Literal Madness - Kathy Acker financial data, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Client project: Literal Madness - Kathy Acker notes and scraps, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Client project: Literal Madness - Kathy Acker expenses, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Client project: Paris Peasant - Aragon, Louis, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Client project: Aurelia, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Client project: In a Different Light press release info - Blake, Rinder and Scholder, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Client project: Breaking Through, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Client project: Resisting the Virtual Life press material - Brook and Boal, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Client project: Closer - Dennis Cooper book tour info, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Client project: Closer - Dennis Cooper mailing and book requests, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Client project: Closer - Dennis Cooper financia; data, testimonials, interview schedules, reviews, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Client project: Closer - Dennis Cooper expenses, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Client project: Closer - Dennis Cooper galley mailing, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Client project: City of God - Cuadros, Gil, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Client project: Horror Hospital - Cooper, Dennis, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Client project: Counterculture - exhibition press, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Client project: material for Ethyl Eichekberger book, 1986-1996 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Client project: Howl and Other Poems - Ginsburg, Allen, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Client project: The New World Border - Gomez-Pena, Guillermo, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Client project: The Alphabet Man - Grossman, Richard press releases, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Client project: The Alphabet Man - Grossman, Richard general publicity, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 31)